Faculty of Science fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Dean's administrative records and correspondence, 1965 - 2000; F-24-1; 5.04 m of textual records
  - Faculty of Science administrative records, 1966 - 1998; F-24-1-5; 1.24 m of textual records
    - National Research Council - Nuffield Lectureship, 1972 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-15)
    - National Research Council - Nuffield Lectureship, 1973 - 1974; F-24-1-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-15)
    - National Research Council - Awards and scholarships, 1974 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-15)
    - National Research Council - Awards, scholarships, applications, 1975; F-24-1-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 24-15)
    - National Research Council - Awards policy and winners, 1969 - 1973; F-24-1-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 24-15)
    - National Research Council - Awards and applications, 1973; F-24-1-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 24-15)
    - CAUT dispute, 1968; F-24-1-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - CAUT censure, 1968 - 1969; F-24-1-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - CAUT censure, 1968 - 1969; F-24-1-5-0-27 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - CAUT censure, 1968 - 1969; F-24-1-5-0-28 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - Policies, practices and procedures, 1966 - 1973; F-24-1-5-0-29 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - Policies, practices and procedures, 1969; F-24-1-5-0-30 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - Goals and objectives, 1969; F-24-1-5-0-31 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - Procedures for selecting Deans/Associate Deans, 1969 - 1972; F-24-1-5-0-32 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - Policies, practices and procedures, 1970; F-24-1-5-0-33 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - Committee lists, 1973; F-24-1-5-0-34 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-5-8.
    - Policies, practices and procedures, 1974; F-24-1-5-0-35 (Archival box - standard 24-16)
    - Course proposal Space Science minor, 1977; F-24-1-5-0-36 (Archival box - standard 24-17)
    - Research Park, vol. 1, 1977 - 1979; F-24-1-5-0-37 (Archival box - standard 24-17)
    - Research Park, vol. 2, 1977 - 1979; F-24-1-5-0-38 (Archival box - standard 24-17)
    - Animal Care Facility, 1977 - 1983; F-24-1-5-0-39 (Archival box - standard 24-17)
    - Phase Four Science Complex specifications, vol. 1, 1978; F-24-1-5-0-40 (Archival box - standard 24-17)
    - Phase Four Science Complex specifications, vol. 2, 1978; F-24-1-5-0-41 (Archival box - standard 24-17)
    - Promoting Better Understanding and Improving Interactions Between the Science Faculty and Industry, 1979; F-24-1-5-0-42 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - B.C. Science Council correspondence, 1979; F-24-1-5-0-43 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - Research activities, 1979 - 1981; F-24-1-5-0-44 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - Research Park, vol. 1, 1979 - 1982; F-24-1-5-0-45 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - Research Park, vol. 2, 1979 - 1982; F-24-1-5-0-46 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - Albert Einstein Centennial Lectures, 1979 - 1984; F-24-1-5-0-47 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - B.C. Science Council correspondence, 1980; F-24-1-5-0-48 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - Diving regulations, 1980 - 1983; F-24-1-5-0-49 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - Chemical Ecology Research Group proposal, 1980 - 1984; F-24-1-5-0-50 (Archival box - standard 24-18)
    - B.C. Science Council correspondence, 1981; F-24-1-5-0-51 (Archival box - standard 24-19)
    - Faculty of Science major projects, 1981; F-24-1-5-0-52 (Archival box - standard 24-19)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-2-22.
    - Research Park: University-Industrial Liaison, 1981 - 1984; F-24-1-5-0-53 (Archival box - standard 24-19)
      Creator's original file classification code: E-5-5.
    - Science Day, 1982; F-24-1-5-0-54 (Archival box - standard 24-19)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-1-6a.
    - Amalgamated Science Stores, 1982 - 1983; F-24-1-5-0-55 (Archival box - standard 24-19)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-2-25.
    - China visit, 1983; F-24-1-5-0-56 (Archival box - standard 24-19)
      Creator's original file classification code: E-6-4.
    - Science Stores reorganization, 1983 - 1984; F-24-1-5-0-57 (Archival box - standard 24-19)
    - Science Stores correspondence, 1983 - 1985; F-24-1-5-0-58 (Archival box - standard 24-19)
      Creator's original file classification code: 1.9.
    - TRIUMF, 1986 - 1996; F-24-1-5-0-59 (Archival box - standard 24-20)
    - Masters program in Aquaculture, vol. 1, 1987 - 1995; F-24-1-5-0-60 (Archival box - standard 24-20)
      Creator's original file classification code: 2.1.5.1.0.
    - Masters program in Aquaculture, vol. 2, 1987 - 1995; F-24-1-5-0-61 (Archival box - standard 24-20)
    - Masters program in Aquaculture, vol. 3, 1987 - 1995; F-24-1-5-0-62 (Archival box - standard 24-20)
    - KAON Factory (TRIUMF), vol. 1, 1988 - 1994; F-24-1-5-0-63 (Archival box - standard 24-20)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.1.2.4.0.
    - KAON Factory (TRIUMF), vol. 2, 1988 - 1994; F-24-1-5-0-64 (Archival box - standard 24-20)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.1.2.4.1.
    - Strategic planning, 1989 - 1990; F-24-1-5-0-65 (Archival box - standard 24-21)
    - Fraser Valley initiative, 1989 - 1997; F-24-1-5-0-66 (Archival box - standard 24-21)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.3.3.0.0.
    - Hydrogen initiative, vol. 1, 1990 - 1991; F-24-1-5-0-67 (Archival box - standard 24-21)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.7.2.0.0.
    - Hydrogen initiative, vol. 2, 1990 - 1991; F-24-1-5-0-68 (Archival box - standard 24-21)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.7.2.0.1.
    - University College of the Fraser Valley degree proposals, 1992 - 1993; F-24-1-5-0-69 (Archival box - standard 24-21)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.3.3.1.1.
    - Chilean universities collaborations, vol. 1, 1992 - 1996; F-24-1-5-0-70 (Archival box - standard 24-21)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.4.4.0.0.
    - Chilean universities collaborations, vol. 2, 1992 - 1996; F-24-1-5-0-71 (Archival box - standard 24-22)
    - Chilean universities collaborations, vol. 3, 1992 - 1996; F-24-1-5-0-72 (Archival box - standard 24-22)
    - Chilean universities collaborations, vol. 4, 1992 - 1996; F-24-1-5-0-73 (Archival box - standard 24-22)
    - Chilean universities collaborations, vol. 5, 1992 - 1996; F-24-1-5-0-74 (Archival box - standard 24-22)
    - University College of the Fraser Valley B.Sc. Degree program, vol. 1, 1992 - 1998; F-24-1-5-0-75 (Archival box - standard 24-22)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.3.3.1.0.
    - University College of the Fraser Valley B.Sc. Degree program, vol. 2, 1992 - 1998; F-24-1-5-0-76 (Archival box - standard 24-22)
    - University College of the Fraser Valley B.Sc. Degree program, vol. 3, 1992 - 1998; F-24-1-5-0-77 (Archival box - standard 24-22)
    - Science Alive! Final report, 1996; F-24-1-5-0-78 (Archival box - standard 24-23)
    - Science Alive! Final report, 1997; F-24-1-5-0-79 (Archival box - standard 24-23)
  - Eastern Islands University Development Project, 1988 - 1996; F-24-1-6; 37 cm of textual records
    - Personnel, vol. 1, 1988 - 1993; F-24-1-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-23)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.7.1.1.1.
    - Personnel, vol. 2, 1988 - 1993; F-24-1-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-23)
    - Advisory Committee, vol. 1, 1989 - 1995; F-24-1-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-23)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.7.1.1.2.
    - Advisory Committee, vol. 2, 1989 - 1995; F-24-1-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-23)
    - Advisory Committee, vol. 3, 1989 - 1995; F-24-1-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-24)
    - Advisory Committee, vol. 4, 1989 - 1995; F-24-1-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-24)
    - Project correspondence and reports, 1989; F-24-1-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-24)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.7.1.1.0.
    - Project correspondence and reports, 1990; F-24-1-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-24)
    - Project planning - phase 2, vol. 1, 1990 - 1993; F-24-1-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-24)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.7.1.3.0.
    - Project planning - phase 2, vol. 2, 1990 - 1993; F-24-1-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-25)
    - Project correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1991; F-24-1-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-25)
    - Project correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1991; F-24-1-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-25)
    - Project correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1992; F-24-1-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-25)
    - Project correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1992; F-24-1-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-25)
    - Project correspondence and reports, 1993; F-24-1-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
    - Project planning - phase 2, vol. 1, 1994 - 1996; F-24-1-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
    - Project planning - phase 2, vol. 2, 1994 - 1996; F-24-1-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
  - Faculty of Science meetings, 1965 - 1988; F-24-1-7; 57 cm of textual records
    - Index, 1965 - 1966; F-24-1-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1965; F-24-1-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1966; F-24-1-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1966; F-24-1-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1966; F-24-1-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1967; F-24-1-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-26)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1967; F-24-1-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1967; F-24-1-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1968; F-24-1-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1968; F-24-1-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1968; F-24-1-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1968; F-24-1-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1968; F-24-1-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1969; F-24-1-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1969; F-24-1-7-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1970; F-24-1-7-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1970; F-24-1-7-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1970; F-24-1-7-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1970; F-24-1-7-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-27)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1970; F-24-1-7-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1971; F-24-1-7-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1971; F-24-1-7-0-22 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-1-7-0-23 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-1-7-0-24 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1973; F-24-1-7-0-25 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1973; F-24-1-7-0-26 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1974; F-24-1-7-0-27 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1974; F-24-1-7-0-28 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1974; F-24-1-7-0-29 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1975; F-24-1-7-0-30 (Archival box - standard 24-28)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1975; F-24-1-7-0-31 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1976; F-24-1-7-0-32 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1976; F-24-1-7-0-33 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1977; F-24-1-7-0-34 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1977; F-24-1-7-0-35 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1977; F-24-1-7-0-36 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1978; F-24-1-7-0-37 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1978; F-24-1-7-0-38 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1979; F-24-1-7-0-39 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1979; F-24-1-7-0-40 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1979; F-24-1-7-0-41 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1979; F-24-1-7-0-42 (Archival box - standard 24-29)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1980; F-24-1-7-0-43 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1981; F-24-1-7-0-44 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1982; F-24-1-7-0-45 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1983; F-24-1-7-0-46 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1984; F-24-1-7-0-47 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1985; F-24-1-7-0-48 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1986; F-24-1-7-0-49 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1987 - 1988; F-24-1-7-0-50 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
  - Faculty of Science Chairmen's meetings, 1979 - 1986; F-24-1-8; 14 cm of textual records
    - Chairmen correspondence, 1979 - 1982; F-24-1-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-30)
    - Chairmen correspondence, 1983 - 1984; F-24-1-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-31)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-2-1.
    - Chairmen correspondence, 1984; F-24-1-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-31)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.3.
    - Chairmen meetings, vol. 1, 1984; F-24-1-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-31)
    - Chairmen meetings, vol. 2, 1984; F-24-1-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-31)
    - Chairmen correspondence, 1985; F-24-1-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-31)
    - Chairmen meetings, vol. 1, 1985 - 1986; F-24-1-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-31)
    - Chairmen meetings, vol. 2, 1985 - 1986; F-24-1-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-31)
  - Departmental correspondence - Biology, 1967 - 1995; F-24-1-9; 74 cm of textual records
    - Departmental correspondence - Biology, 1967 - 1992; F-24-1-9-1; 24 cm of textual records
      - Pestology - correspondence, 1967 - 1969; F-24-1-9-1-1 (Archival box - standard 24-59)
      - Biological Sciences - correspondence, 1968 - 1975; F-24-1-9-1-2 (Archival box - standard 24-59)
      - Pestology - correspondence, 1970 - 1975; F-24-1-9-1-3 (Archival box - standard 24-59)
      - Biochemistry and Biophysics - correspondence, 1971 - 1974; F-24-1-9-1-4 (Archival box - standard 24-59)
      - Pestology - correspondence, 1975 - 1979; F-24-1-9-1-5 (Archival box - standard 24-59)
        Creator's original file classification code: F-3-9.
      - Biological Sciences - Current Research Interests of the Faculty, 1976; F-24-1-9-1-6 (Archival box - standard 24-59)
      - Biological Sciences - graduate studies brochure, 1977; F-24-1-9-1-7 (Archival box - standard 24-59)
      - Pestology - correspondence, vol. 1, 1979 - 1984; F-24-1-9-1-8 (Archival box - standard 24-60)
      - Pestology - correspondence, vol. 2, 1979 - 1984; F-24-1-9-1-9 (Archival box - standard 24-60)
      - Bioscience Update '82 - correspondence, 1982; F-24-1-9-1-10 (Archival box - standard 24-60)
      - Center for Pest Management, 1982 - 1984; F-24-1-9-1-11 (Archival box - standard 24-60)
        Creator's original file classification code: F-2-24.
      - Biochemistry program review, 1983 - 1985; F-24-1-9-1-12 (Archival box - standard 24-60)
        Creator's original file classification code: 2.1.16.
      - Center for Pest Management (Pestology), 1984 - 1985; F-24-1-9-1-13 (Archival box - standard 24-60)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.3.2.
      - Institute of Biochemistry and Molecular Biology, 1985 - 1987; F-24-1-9-1-14 (Archival box - standard 24-60)
      - Biotechnology Master's Program, 1986 - 1991; F-24-1-9-1-15 (Archival box - standard 24-60)
        Creator's original file classification code: 2.1.8.1.0.
      - Institute of Biochemistry and Molecular Biology, 1987 - 1992; F-24-1-9-1-16 (Archival box - standard 24-61)
        Creator's original file classification code: 2.1.8.0.0.
    - Western Canadian Universities Marine Biology Society (WCUMBS), 1969 - 1995; F-24-1-9-2; 50 cm of textual records
      - Bamfield Marine Station publications, 1969 - 1987; F-24-1-9-2-1 (Archival box - standard 24-61)
      - Policies and legal certificates, 1970 - 1980; F-24-1-9-2-2 (Archival box - standard 24-61)
        Creator's original file classification code: F-3-8.
      - Correspondence and reports, 1977 - 1979; F-24-1-9-2-3 (Archival box - standard 24-61)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, 1977 - 1983; F-24-1-9-2-4 (Archival box - standard 24-61)
      - Correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1980 - 1984; F-24-1-9-2-5 (Archival box - standard 24-61)
      - Correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1980 - 1984; F-24-1-9-2-6 (Archival box - standard 24-61)
      - WCUMBS Executive Committee meetings, 1984 - 1985; F-24-1-9-2-7 (Archival box - standard 24-62)
      - WCUMBS Board of Management meetings, 1984 - 1985; F-24-1-9-2-8 (Archival box - standard 24-62)
      - WCUMBS Finance Committee meetings, 1985; F-24-1-9-2-9 (Archival box - standard 24-62)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1985; F-24-1-9-2-10 (Archival box - standard 24-62)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, 1986; F-24-1-9-2-11 (Archival box - standard 24-62)
      - WCUMBS AGM meeting, 1987; F-24-1-9-2-12 (Archival box - standard 24-62)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, 1987; F-24-1-9-2-13 (Archival box - standard 24-62)
      - WCUMBS Finance Committee correspondence, 1987 - 1994; F-24-1-9-2-14 (Archival box - standard 24-62)
        Creator's original file classification code: 4.1.1.2.0.
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, vol. 1, 1988; F-24-1-9-2-15 (Archival box - standard 24-63)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, vol. 2, 1988; F-24-1-9-2-16 (Archival box - standard 24-63)
      - WCUMBS Management Council correspondence, 1988 - 1994; F-24-1-9-2-17 (Archival box - standard 24-63)
        Creator's original file classification code: 4.1.1.1.0.
      - Bamfield Review, 1991 - 1992; F-24-1-9-2-18 (Archival box - standard 24-63)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, vol. 1, 1992; F-24-1-9-2-19 (Archival box - standard 24-63)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, vol. 2, 1992; F-24-1-9-2-20 (Archival box - standard 24-63)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, vol. 1, 1993; F-24-1-9-2-21 (Archival box - standard 24-63)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, vol. 2, 1993; F-24-1-9-2-22 (Archival box - standard 24-63)
      - WCUMBS NSERC application, 1993; F-24-1-9-2-23 (Archival box - standard 24-64)
      - Eco-physiology Lab, 1993 - 1994; F-24-1-9-2-24 (Archival box - standard 24-64)
      - WCUMBS background information, 1994; F-24-1-9-2-25 (Archival box - standard 24-64)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, vol. 1, 1994; F-24-1-9-2-26 (Archival box - standard 24-64)
      - WCUMBS Management Council meetings, vol. 2, 1994; F-24-1-9-2-27 (Archival box - standard 24-64)
      - WCUMBS NSERC application, 1994; F-24-1-9-2-28 (Archival box - standard 24-64)
      - WCUMBS background information, 1995; F-24-1-9-2-29 (Archival box - standard 24-64)
        Creator's original file classification code: 4.1.1.1.0..
      - WCUMBS NSERC application, 1995; F-24-1-9-2-30 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
  - Departmental correspondence - Chemistry, 1974 - 1986; F-24-1-10; 11 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1974 - 1976; F-24-1-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-8-3b.
    - Chemistry Newsletter, 1978; F-24-1-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-4-8.
    - Correspondence, 1979 - 1986; F-24-1-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
    - NMR Spectrometer, 1980 - 1984; F-24-1-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-4-10.
    - Communications Newsletter, 1980 - 1986; F-24-1-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
    - Chemistry in the '80's seminars, 1981; F-24-1-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
    - Chemistry in the '80's seminars, 1982 - 1983; F-24-1-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
    - Department of Chemistry Safety Manual, 1983; F-24-1-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-65)
  - University Research Institutes, 1978 - 1996; F-24-1-11; 13 cm of textual records
    - Theoretical Science Institute, 1978 - 1983; F-24-1-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-66)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-2-16.
    - Institute for Energy, 1979 - 1994; F-24-1-11-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-66)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-2-18.
    - Institute for Aquaculture Research, vol. 1, 1987 - 1996; F-24-1-11-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-66)
      Creator's original file classification code: 2.1.5.0.0..
    - Institute for Aquaculture Research, vol. 2, 1987 - 1996; F-24-1-11-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-66)
    - Institute for Aquaculture Research, vol. 3, 1987 - 1996; F-24-1-11-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-66)
    - Applied Mathematics Institute (proposed), 1990 - 1993; F-24-1-11-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-66)
      Creator's original file classification code: 2.9.2.0.0.
    - Environmental Science Research Institute, 1991 - 1996; F-24-1-11-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-66)
      Creator's original file classification code: 2.1.1.2.2.
  - South Science Building, 1988 - 1994; F-24-1-12; 13 cm of textual records
    - Dean's correspondence and reports, 1988; F-24-1-12-0-1 (Archival box - small 24-67)
    - Dean's correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1989; F-24-1-12-0-2 (Archival box - small 24-67)
    - Dean's correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1989; F-24-1-12-0-3 (Archival box - small 24-67)
    - Dean's correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1990; F-24-1-12-0-4 (Archival box - small 24-68)
    - Dean's correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1990; F-24-1-12-0-5 (Archival box - small 24-68)
    - Dean's correspondence and reports, 1991 - 1992; F-24-1-12-0-6 (Archival box - small 24-68)
    - Dean's correspondence and reports, 1993 - 1994; F-24-1-12-0-7 (Archival box - small 24-68)
- Faculty research information, 1967 - 1975; F-24-2; 6 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to faculty members, including staff lists, workload reports, and teaching evaluations. Records include correspondence, working papers, and reports.
  No further accruals are expected as this series is closed.
  - Faculty work loads, 1975; F-24-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - small 24-32)
  - Faculty work loads - budget, 1967; F-24-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - small 24-32)
  - Faculty work loads - budget, 1968 - 1972; F-24-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - small 24-32)
  - Associates in Science, 1971 - 1972; F-24-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - small 24-32)
  - Teaching evaluations, 1972 - 1974; F-24-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - small 24-32)
  - Staffing, 1974; F-24-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - small 24-32)
- Faculty committee records, 1966 - 1995; F-24-3; 2.68 m of textual records